export const data = [
  {
    "question": "When will I receive my security deposit amount?",
    "answer": "Security deposit refund will be initiated within 7 business days after the date of return of the bike/ car. In case of any damages / violations, any eligible refund may get delayed slightly to incorporate the correct charges from the violations."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I get the car or bike with full tank fuel at the time of booking?",
    "answer": "No. The fuel in the vehicle given to you is at an x point out of y points and the same level of fuel is to be returned back, while returning the vehicle. Vehicle returned with short fuel quantity will result in the fuel cost + 25% surcharge being levied. This will be as per the assessment of the 4 Wheel Travels team and GST is extra."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I get reimbursement, if vehicle returned with extra fuel?",
    "answer": "No, there won't be any refund for the extra fuel nor there will be any adjustment in the bill. (in terms of Extra km's & Extra Hours)"
  },
  {
    "question": "What happens to my security deposit if vehicle is returned with damage?",
    "answer": "It depends on the damage and on the vehicle type and insurance is triggered only beyond a certain threshold limit described in the agreement and even then, there will be a certain liability assessed by 4 Wheel Travels to factor insurance short payment, NCB loss, business loss, vehicle depreciation, etc. This amount will be as per the assessment of the 4 Wheel Travels team and GST extra."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I change my plan in between the rental period?",
    "answer": "No, the plan can't be changed once the vehicle is on booking. Need to select the plan before booking itself."
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I need to pay the border taxes?",
    "answer": "Yes, border tax, toll gate charges and any other challans you will be liable to pay."
  },
  {
    "question": "I am paying my rental and security deposit through cash, can I get a refund immediately after returning the car?",
    "answer": "No. The refund will be made within 7 working days in your bank account."
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the policy if the user exceeds the 24 hrs?",
    "answer": "We will charge on an hourly basis for the first two hours. After 2 hrs there is an additional day charge will be levied. In case of extra hour being charged, there is no free km eligible in the hours."
  },
  {
    "question": "Please give me the car with a full tank and I will return you with a full tank.",
    "answer": "We will attempt to do that but cannot assure that the same will be ensured."
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there any taxes extra?",
    "answer": "The published pricing of 4 Wheel Travels is inclusive of GST as applicable. This has been made to ensure absolutely ease and clarity of cost. However, other tangibles like damages, fuel cost, challans, etc., may/will be subject to GST over and above the incurred or stated cost."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I speed on the vehicles?",
    "answer": "Government-mandated speed restrictions apply in all cases without any exceptions and where there is a lack of clarity, 4 Wheel Travels has enforced a max of 120 kmph as the speed limit. Violations are subject to penalties and repeated violations may also result in additional penalties or even the Security deposit can be forfeited and the user will be banned from the 4 Wheel Travels ecosystem for car and bike rentals."
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the policy on traffic challans?",
    "answer": "The challans incurred during the rental period are liable to be paid by the user and have to be cleared without any delay immediately. In case the user decides to pay 4 Wheel Travels for the same, the challan + convenience fee + any applicable GST will be levied."
  },
  {
    "question": "What documents are required to pick up a vehicle at the location?",
    "answer": "For a seamless experience, we suggest you upload your documents while booking itself so that they can be verified. The documents will also be physically verified at the time of pick-up. You need to upload the front and back of each document. In case you don't have an Aadhar card, please upload a copy of your passport for verification purpose."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the eligibility of age to hire a car?",
    "answer": "Minimum age to hire self-drive car is 21 years. Apart from that, the customer should have a valid and original driving licence with LMV (low motor vehicle)."
  },
  {
    "question": "What if I am travelling to India and want to rent a car?",
    "answer": "For foreign nationals, an international driving permit is required in addition to the driving licence."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can my friend or relative pick the vehicle?",
    "answer": "No, only the person whose name is mentioned in the reservation form needs to come along with the required documents to pick the vehicle."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is included in my booking rental amount?",
    "answer": "Our prices include the rental charges inclusive of GST. Our prices do not include tolls, inter-state taxes and parking. No hidden charges!"
  },
  {
    "question": "What if the car gets damaged by a third party?",
    "answer": "The renter (who has booked the car) is completely liable for any damage done by a third party."
  },
  {
    "question": "What should be done if a car gets a breakdown?",
    "answer": "In case the car gets a breakdown, firstly reach out to our customer care executive of the concerned location who will help you arrange for the towing of the vehicle. You need to arrange to tow the vehicle to the nearby authorised service center. Towing charges will be paid from your end. You need to visit the nearby police station to lodge FIR in local police / a copy of the intimation letter provided by local police authority, and the same should be handed over to our office from where you have picked the vehicle. We will guide you through the entire process. Do not leave the place of breakdown until all formalities have been completed. Vehicle documents are to be kept safely with you and it should be handed over along with FIR copy to the location from where you have picked the vehicle."
  },
  {
    "question": "What if the car gets stolen?",
    "answer": "A police complaint needs to be registered immediately & the same needs to be informed to us. A copy of FIR/intimation letter acknowledged by police authority needs to be submitted to our office."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I get the vehicle type and variant I have booked?",
    "answer": "4 Wheel Travels clients relish the range offered to them by 4 Wheel Travels and we make our best effort to ensure that the client gets what they have booked. But sometimes, for reasons beyond our control, like client extensions for unforeseen reasons, vehicle damages, etc., we may not be able to give what's booked. We will then provide a similar segment vehicle or one from the closest segment possible. This is done to avoid any last min. Changes to the client's schedule because of a non-availability of the model chosen."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the policy to get a vehicle dropped at my location & pick up from my location?",
    "answer": "We do provide the required service on a chargeable basis. Charges depend on the distance of your preferred location from our hub. The same will be displayed on our app during booking itself. Booking Time, Kilometre's reading & fuel level will be calculated from our hub & same will be applicable for closing the booking, i.e., time, kilometre's reading & fuel level will be closed at our hub. The charge is for the service and the vehicle parameters are from our hub and back to our hub."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do I need to consider while selecting the drop & pick up option?",
    "answer": "Please consider the travel time from our hub to your preferred location while planning your travel. Example - if you are planning to start your trip from your home at 18.00 hrs & your preferred location is 10 kms from our hub, you may select your booking time at 17.00 hrs, so that we will start the vehicle from our hub at 17.00 hrs to deliver the vehicle at your location as per your plan & same should be for the pickup from your location for the travel back to the hub."
  }
]

export const cheuffeurData = [
  {
    "question": "How can I book?",
    "answer": "You can share your requirement using our booking tool on our website. Alternatively, you can send us an email with your requirements to bookings@4wheeltravels.com, we will book the car for you& a confirmation mail will be sent to you. You can also reach us on 040-44774477 / +91 98853 54321"
  },
  {
    "question": "How far in advance should I book my travel?",
    "answer": "We suggest booking as early as possible to get the best discount. For online bookings, you can book up to 24 hours before the travel. If you need a car sooner, then you need to contact us via email / connect with us on WhatsApp."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are your payment methods?",
    "answer": "You will pay with your card via online payment. Regular customers can also pay cash or thru UPI. Bank transfers are also possible."
  },
  {
    "question": "Where will I meet my driver at Airport?",
    "answer": "Our chauffeur will wait for you in arrivals and will hold a placard with your name on it. It is always easy to spot location. If you have any problem with locating a driver, please give him a call on his mobile, which you receive once the booking is allocated."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will you give me the chauffeurs name and a contact number?",
    "answer": "You will receive the driver details once he is allocated to the job. Usually, it's going to be 2-3 hours before starting of the vehicle from our garage."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will my chauffeur drive safely and obey all traffic laws?",
    "answer": "Our chauffeurs are trained at driving to the highest standards. When you ride with us, safety comes first. We feature the latest safety equipment on all of our vehicles and always drive within the allowed speed limit."
  },
  {
    "question": "Are your chauffeurs and vehicles fully licensed and insured to carry passengers?",
    "answer": "All drivers and vehicles are fully licensed by Transport Authority. Vehicle &Drivers are comprehensively insured."
  },
  // {
  //   "question": "What's the policy if the user exceeds the 24 hrs?",
  //   "answer": "We will charge on an hourly basis for the first two hours. After 2 hrs there is an additional day charge will be levied. In case of extra hour being charged, there is no free km eligible in the hours."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "Please give me the car with a full tank and I will return you with a full tank.",
  //   "answer": "We will attempt to do that but cannot assure that the same will be ensured."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "Are there any taxes extra?",
  //   "answer": "The published pricing of 4 Wheel Travels is inclusive of GST as applicable. This has been made to ensure absolutely ease and clarity of cost. However, other tangibles like damages, fuel cost, challans, etc., may/will be subject to GST over and above the incurred or stated cost."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "Can I speed on the vehicles?",
  //   "answer": "Government-mandated speed restrictions apply in all cases without any exceptions and where there is a lack of clarity, 4 Wheel Travels has enforced a max of 120 kmph as the speed limit. Violations are subject to penalties and repeated violations may also result in additional penalties or even the Security deposit can be forfeited and the user will be banned from the 4 Wheel Travels ecosystem for car and bike rentals."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What's the policy on traffic challans?",
  //   "answer": "The challans incurred during the rental period are liable to be paid by the user and have to be cleared without any delay immediately. In case the user decides to pay 4 Wheel Travels for the same, the challan + convenience fee + any applicable GST will be levied."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What documents are required to pick up a vehicle at the location?",
  //   "answer": "For a seamless experience, we suggest you upload your documents while booking itself so that they can be verified. The documents will also be physically verified at the time of pick-up. You need to upload the front and back of each document. In case you don't have an Aadhar card, please upload a copy of your passport for verification purpose."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What is the eligibility of age to hire a car?",
  //   "answer": "Minimum age to hire self-drive car is 21 years. Apart from that, the customer should have a valid and original driving licence with LMV (low motor vehicle)."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What if I am travelling to India and want to rent a car?",
  //   "answer": "For foreign nationals, an international driving permit is required in addition to the driving licence."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "Can my friend or relative pick the vehicle?",
  //   "answer": "No, only the person whose name is mentioned in the reservation form needs to come along with the required documents to pick the vehicle."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What is included in my booking rental amount?",
  //   "answer": "Our prices include the rental charges inclusive of GST. Our prices do not include tolls, inter-state taxes and parking. No hidden charges!"
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What if the car gets damaged by a third party?",
  //   "answer": "The renter (who has booked the car) is completely liable for any damage done by a third party."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What should be done if a car gets a breakdown?",
  //   "answer": "In case the car gets a breakdown, firstly reach out to our customer care executive of the concerned location who will help you arrange for the towing of the vehicle. You need to arrange to tow the vehicle to the nearby authorised service center. Towing charges will be paid from your end. You need to visit the nearby police station to lodge FIR in local police / a copy of the intimation letter provided by local police authority, and the same should be handed over to our office from where you have picked the vehicle. We will guide you through the entire process. Do not leave the place of breakdown until all formalities have been completed. Vehicle documents are to be kept safely with you and it should be handed over along with FIR copy to the location from where you have picked the vehicle."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What if the car gets stolen?",
  //   "answer": "A police complaint needs to be registered immediately & the same needs to be informed to us. A copy of FIR/intimation letter acknowledged by police authority needs to be submitted to our office."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "Will I get the vehicle type and variant I have booked?",
  //   "answer": "4 Wheel Travels clients relish the range offered to them by 4 Wheel Travels and we make our best effort to ensure that the client gets what they have booked. But sometimes, for reasons beyond our control, like client extensions for unforeseen reasons, vehicle damages, etc., we may not be able to give what's booked. We will then provide a similar segment vehicle or one from the closest segment possible. This is done to avoid any last min. Changes to the client's schedule because of a non-availability of the model chosen."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What is the policy to get a vehicle dropped at my location & pick up from my location?",
  //   "answer": "We do provide the required service on a chargeable basis. Charges depend on the distance of your preferred location from our hub. The same will be displayed on our app during booking itself. Booking Time, Kilometre's reading & fuel level will be calculated from our hub & same will be applicable for closing the booking, i.e., time, kilometre's reading & fuel level will be closed at our hub. The charge is for the service and the vehicle parameters are from our hub and back to our hub."
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "What do I need to consider while selecting the drop & pick up option?",
  //   "answer": "Please consider the travel time from our hub to your preferred location while planning your travel. Example - if you are planning to start your trip from your home at 18.00 hrs & your preferred location is 10 kms from our hub, you may select your booking time at 17.00 hrs, so that we will start the vehicle from our hub at 17.00 hrs to deliver the vehicle at your location as per your plan & same should be for the pickup from your location for the travel back to the hub."
  // }
]

